bd-natok.com 2012-09-15

# Bdbangla.org Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy For Amaderbangladesh.com  
We Are Committed To Your Privacy  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. The Information We Collect From You:  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concernwebsite. The types of personal information collected when you sign up are:  
(user) Name  
Email address  
Home Page (optional)  
Random information that you provide (optional)  
The Way We Use Information:  
We use the information you provide about yourself when registering to verify that you have requested access to our site. We do not share this information with outside parties - EVER. If you activate the "Personal Contact Form" in your account to allow other members to contact you via the site, your email address is not disclosed. All members (including moderators and the site owners) are limited to sending no more than three email messages per hour via the site-contact form. This three-message per hour limit is our way of protecting members from people that may try to use our site for spamming. Note that when sending a message to a member via their contact form, your email address will be disclosed to that member in the "from" address. eMail Address In Forum and Comment Posts:  
To protect your privacy, posting of email address in comments for forum posts is not permitted. All posts containing email address are automatically unpublished and are either deleted or edited to remove the email address before being published. We do this to protect our members from spammers that may harvest your email address from our site. Cookies, 'Web Beacons' and Visitor Data Tracking We may place a 'cookie' on your computer or create a unique "session id" for purposes of remembering your preferences, pages viewed, etc. Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concerndoes not use cookies or session ID's for 'tracking' purposes or for gathering any personally identifiable information about you. If you choose, you may disable cookies in your web-browser to prevent use of such cookies. Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concernuses a combination of web-server logs and third-party analytical data gathering tools for the purposes of aggregate visitor traffic information which may set a cookie on your computer. The data collected by these third-party services may include information such as your IP address, type of web-browser, and computer operating system. Currently Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concernuses the following third-party visitor tracking tools: Google Analytics  
http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concerndoes not use "web beacons" of any kind with the exception of third-party links or advertisers (see next section). Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within our Site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on GrownUpGeek.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see. GrownUpGeek does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks. The advertiser(s) may also use information regarding your use of GrownUpGeek.com, such as the number of times you viewed an ad (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks (see links below) for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. GrownUpGeek.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Currently, Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concernhas relationships with the following third-party ad servers or ad networks:  
Kontera http://kontera.com  
Google, Inc. http:/www.google.com/privacypolicy.html  
Commission Junction http://www.cj.com/privacy.html  
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect and maintain or modify it by clicking the "My Account" link in the upper-left (grey) area of most pages on our website. Our Commitment To Data Security  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Cancellation of services  
You may, at any time request to cancel your account and specify that all your data be removed from our servers. Please note that all posts, comments, or replies made by you on our website become the property of Bdbangla.com or any of its sister concernand will not be removed. Upon removal from our system all posts, comments or replies made by you will be re-attributed to the user "Anonymous". To request cancellation or removal from our system, you may email your request to: kabirfarhad@yahoo.com. How To Contact Us  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies you may contact us via email at: kabirfarhad@yahoo.com. This Policy Is Valid for all the sister sites Related With bdbangla.com. The lists are followings:  
www.bdbangla.com  
www.bd-natok.com  
www.bd-dramaserials.com  
www.tazakhobor.com  
www.amaderbangladesh.com  
www.bd-blogger.com  
www.kolorob.com  
www.banglaralo.com  
www.bd-serials.com  
www.bdbanglabrothers.com  
www.bd-gaan.com  
www.bdbanglablog.com  
www.bdwebdirectory.com  
www.bdbangla.info
